today we are going to talk about Java 9
今天我们要谈论Java 9
obviously the timing of this works
显然，这项工作的时机
really well since Java 9 came out the
自从Java 9诞生以来
last week of the week before very
前一周的最后一周
recently and I'm with Java 1 going on
最近，我正在使用Java 1
this week as well there's an awful lot
这周也有很多
of noise around around Java 9 what it is
Java 9周围的噪音是什么
and how it's going to impact us
以及它将如何影响我们
developers developers so in this webinar
开发人员，因此在此网络研讨会中
that's what we're going to cover as
这就是我们要涵盖的内容
Andrea said so what I always like to do
安德里亚（Andrea）说，所以我一直喜欢做的事
with my presentations is I like to take
我的演讲是我喜欢的
the features which are relevant to us as
与我们相关的功能
developers and show how we're going to
开发人员，并展示我们将如何
use them in our real day-to-day jobs so
在我们实际的日常工作中使用它们，以便
that's why I've called it real-world
这就是为什么我称它为真实世界
Java 9 we're going to have a look at
Java 9我们来看看
jigsaw of course being the big-ticket
拼图当然是大事了
item for Java 9 we're going to have a
Java 9的项目，我们将有一个
quick look at the reactive API in Java 9
快速查看Java 9中的反应式API
and then we're going to cover everything
然后我们将涵盖所有内容
else
其他
unfortunately for Java 9 well for Java
不幸的是，对于Java 9和Java
nines branding the fact is that the
九分品牌的事实是
German line has a lot of different types
德国专线有很多不同的类型
of small changes that make it a
小变化使它成为
difference to us as developers but they
作为开发人员对我们来说是不同的，但他们
don't fall under one nice umbrella turn
不要落入一个好转的伞下
so basically we're going to cover
所以基本上我们将涵盖
everything else whatever that is and we
其他一切，我们
don't have a lot of time so as Andrew
没有很多时间，例如安德鲁
said please feel free to put all the
说请随便放所有
questions into the webinar question box
问题放入网络研讨会问题框中
and we will try and address them at the
我们将尝试在
end but what I would like to do is try
结束但是我想做的就是尝试
and cover as many of these features as
并涵盖尽可能多的这些功能
possible during the presentation and
在演示过程中可能
then them and then leave a lot of the
然后他们，然后离开很多
questions for the end firstly of course
当然首先要问的问题
the question is why Java 9 other than
问题是为什么Java 9除了
the fact that it's the latest greatest
这是最新最伟大的事实
thing and we've been waiting for it for
事情，我们一直在等待它
three years
三年
why do you want to upgrade your code to
为什么要将代码升级到
use Java 9 well as usual they've worked
像往常一样正常使用Java 9
really hard on on things like
在诸如此类的事情上真的很努力
performance so even if you don't use any
性能，即使您不使用任何
of the new features any of the new
新功能中的任何新功能
syntax anything you should get a free
语法任何你应该免费的
better performance particularly around
更好的表现，尤其是周围
use of memory they've changed the way
使用内存，他们改变了方式
that strings work so that can take up to
字符串起作用，因此可能占用最多
half the amount of memory it used to are
过去一半的内存是
you get a better performance of locking
您可以获得更好的锁定性能
secure applications graphics and this is
保护应用程序图形，这是
particularly useful really for the
确实对
IntelliJ IDEA sort of stuff as well
IntelliJ IDEA也一样
we've been able to use some of the Java
我们已经能够使用一些Java
9 features to be able to improve the
9个功能可以改善
graphics of of the application itself
应用程序本身的图形
better documentation better use of
更好的文档，更好的使用
hardware in terms of CPU operations
在CPU操作方面的硬件
faster compilation so even without using
更快的编译，因此即使不使用
any of the features we're going to talk
我们要讨论的任何功能
about use
关于使用
Java 9 will probably speed up your
Java 9可能会加快您的速度
application or the compilation of your
应用程序或您的编译
application so it's kind of interesting
应用程序，所以有点有趣
from that point of view other than that
从那个角度来看
when we think about Java 9 we tend to
当我们想到Java 9时，我们倾向于
hear about jigsaw of course we might
听说拼图，我们当然可以
hear a little bit about the repple J
听到一些关于乳头J的信息
shell which we'll look at in a minute
稍后我们将介绍的外壳
and and then we're not really sure if
然后我们不确定是否
there's anything else that's interesting
还有其他有趣的事情
in Java 9 it seems to be that we've
在Java 9中，似乎我们已经
taken
已采取
I don't know nearly 10 years to produce
我不知道生产将近十年
jigsaw and and what else is there in
拼图和还有什么
Java 9
Java 9
well there's one or two things coming
好吧，有一两件事
into Java 9 as I said there's a lot of a
就像我说的那样进入Java 9
lot of features that don't necessarily
很多功能不一定
all fall together under the same
都归于同一个
umbrella so and there's a lot of things
雨伞之类的东西很多
that they've done in the back end in
他们在后端所做的
terms of how they improve the way that
他们如何改善方式的条款
they develop and the JDK itself so a lot
他们开发了JDK本身
of stuff that isn't necessarily visible
不一定是可见的东西
to us as developers but will allow us to
作为开发人员给我们，但将允许我们
get for example better quality builds
例如获得更好的质量
faster that kind of thing so we will
更快的事情，所以我们会
take a look at some of these features in
看看其中的一些功能
this presentation the case study we're
这个演示我们的案例研究
going to look at I like to use real code
看看我喜欢使用真实代码
for these sorts of things we can use
对于这些事情，我们可以使用
snippets of code if you like but I like
代码片段（如果您喜欢，但我喜欢）
to use real real examples of real
用真实的真实例子
applications so that you get a feel for
应用程序，使您对
what it's like to work with in the real
真正与之合作的感觉
world some of you may remember a couple
世界上有些人可能还记得一对
of years ago I used this demo of a Java
几年前，我使用了Java演示
FX UI that's listening to Twitter
FX UI正在听Twitter
responding to data in real time and then
实时响应数据，然后
updating that to heard that Java FX
更新以听到Java FX
dashboard in real time this was designed
实时设计的仪表板
to demonstrate a lot of the java 8
演示很多Java 8
features like lambdas and streams so
像lambdas和streams这样的功能
what I wanted to do is take this
我想做的就是吃这个
application and see what it might what
应用程序，看看会发生什么
benefits it might get from using Java 9
使用Java 9可能会带来的好处
in particular what's interesting about
特别是有趣的是
this is it's architected as a series of
这是它被设计成一系列的
small services so some of this might be
小服务，所以其中一些可能是
useful in terms of things like the
在诸如
reactive API if you're interested in the
如果您对
original application you can see for
您可以看到的原始应用程序
example the the webinar I did on that at
例如我在
this URL loads more information so I'm
该网址加载了更多信息，因此我
not going to go into it in any detail
不会详细介绍
because that's already been covered in a
因为那已经包含在
previous presentation so let's just dive
上一个演示文稿，所以让我们潜入
straight in the thing that we're kind of
直说我们有点
most afraid of potentially is how hard
最害怕的是有多难
will it be to take my existing
拿走我现有的
application and compile it against you
应用程序并针对您进行编译
9 so let's address that straight
9让我们直接解决
straight now let's address that head-on
现在就直接解决这个问题
before we go any further so here's my
在我们继续之前，这是我的
application and this is this is the
应用程序，这是这
application as it was before I did any
像我之前所做的那样申请
migration so if I rebuild this project
迁移，所以如果我重建这个项目
let's see what happens
让我们看看发生了什么
you
您
firstly what it does is it takes a
首先，它要做的是
little while to build so that I sound
一点时间建造，以便我听起来
very quiet on the webinar as its
网络研讨会上非常安静
building it should be able to give me
建立它应该能够给我
some of the errors so one of the first
一些错误，所以第一个
things which may break your code if you
可能会破坏您的代码的事情，如果您
were doing this is apparently underscore
这样做显然是强调
was a perfectly valid identifier in Java
在Java中是完全有效的标识符
8 and pre-job 8 I think a lot of people
8和岗前8我想很多人
didn't really realize this and now they
并没有真正意识到这一点，现在他们
see this they think oh that's quite cool
看到这个，他们认为哦，这很酷
I could use that for all sorts of nasty
我可以用它来做各种讨厌的事
little hacks and but as of Java 9 this
小技巧，但是从Java 9开始
is no longer valid as an identifier this
不再是有效的标识符
is probably going to be used in later
可能会在以后使用
versions of Java for things like maybe
Java版本，例如
making lambda expressions easier to work
使lambda表达式更易于使用
with so of course to fix that all you
当然可以解决所有问题
need to do is you just need to do a
需要做的就是你只需要做一个
rename let's check there we go rename so
重命名，让我们检查一下，我们去重命名，以便
you want to call it something more
你想再称呼它
useful as I'm using the keyboard
当我使用键盘时很有用
shortcuts for IntelliJ IDEA you should
您应该使用IntelliJ IDEA的快捷方式
see them pop up on the bottom with the
看到它们在底部弹出
presentation assistant so of course you
演示助手，所以你当然
just have to rename that to get that to
只需将其重命名即可
compile and just to clarify though
编译只是为了澄清
underscores are still valid inside the
下划线在内部仍然有效
name if you want they're still valid at
名称，如果您希望它们仍然有效
the front of the name if you want if you
如果需要的话，名称的前面
really really want you could still do
真的很希望你仍然可以做
double underscore but that's kind of
双下划线，但这有点
nasty so I do not recommend that so you
讨厌，所以我不建议您
want to call this something useful
想称它为有用的东西
rebuild it see what happens now we're
重建它，看看现在发生了什么
going to start to see some of the errors
将开始看到一些错误
that we've been told about we've been
我们被告知我们已经
warned about this as people have been
警告人们，因为这已经
talking about Java 9 the point one of
谈论Java 9的要点之一
the main points about jigsaw and
关于拼图和
modularity is the ability to better
模块化是更好的能力
encapsulate better encapsulate your code
更好地封装您的代码
to add a level of protection between
在两者之间增加保护等级
packaged private and public things and
打包私人和公共物品，以及
one of the things that's going away is
即将消失的一件事是
internal API is inside the JVM itself so
内部API位于JVM本身内部，因此
anything that started with some misc we
任何以杂项开头的东西
shouldn't have been using that in the
不应该在
first place but some of us were this is
第一名，但我们当中有些人是
genuine code I was using in my previous
我以前使用的真实代码
application and I was using this base64
应用程序，我正在使用此base64
encode er because it did what I wanted
编码er，因为它做了我想要的
it to do and I
它要做，我
too lazy to find out what I should have
懒得找出我应该拥有的东西
been using instead but Java eight will
一直在使用Java 8
warn you you shouldn't be using this
警告您不应该使用此
because this is an internal API and it
因为这是一个内部API
is going to go away in the later version
在以后的版本中将会消失
so let's get rid of that because we
所以让我们摆脱它，因为我们
don't want to be using that and let's
不想使用它，让我们
replace it with what we should be using
用我们应该使用的替换它
instead in this case what we should be
相反，在这种情况下，我们应该
using is basically for Java dot util get
使用基本上是针对Java dot util get
encoder encode to string and then that
编码器编码为字符串，然后
will all work the way it used to before
都能像以前一样工作
and if I recompile
如果我重新编译
my whole project should compile
我的整个项目应该编译
correctly now so I had to do just two
现在正确，所以我只需要做两个
very small things to try and get my
尝试让我的东西很小
project compiling and both of those
项目编译以及两者
things will give you warnings when
事情会在警告您时
you're compiling it in Java 8 you'll see
您正在使用Java 8进行编译，您将看到
warnings anyway so you can migrate your
无论如何都会发出警告，因此您可以迁移自己的
code to be ready for Java 9 while you're
您可以在Java 9中准备好代码
still using Java 8 and as I said things
仍然使用Java 8，正如我所说的
like the Sun misc packages you shouldn't
像Sun杂项包一样，您不应该
have been using that anyway there is an
一直在使用那个
exception you may have heard that Sun
您可能听说过Sun
dot misc duh unsafe was going away and
不安全的杂点
that's not necessarily the case because
不一定是这样，因为
so I'm not mr. unsafe doesn't have a
所以我不是先生不安全的没有
one-for-one replacement in JDK 9 so they
JDK 9中的一对一替换
couldn't remove unsafe in JDK 9 because
无法删除JDK 9中的不安全原因，因为
there's nothing to replace it with and
没有什么可以替换为和
then although you may not be using it in
然后，尽管您可能不使用它
your code some libraries and frameworks
您的代码一些库和框架
we're using it but what you do need to
我们正在使用它，但是您需要做什么
do is you do need to say yes I really do
你需要做的是，我真的是
want to use unsafe I know what I'm doing
要使用不安全的设备，我知道我在做什么
so that's why it says it's declared in
这就是为什么它说它在
module JDK door unsupported but it's
JDK门模块不受支持，但是
still there but libraries and frameworks
仍然存在，但是库和框架
will be moving away from using that so
将不再使用它，所以
now our code compiles and that really
现在我们的代码可以编译了
wasn't quite as challenging as we
不像我们那么具有挑战性
thought it would be so let's go straight
以为会的，所以让我们直走
onto jigsaw this is the big ticket item
到拼图上，这是大门票项目
for Java 9 jigsaw actually is the name
Java 9拼图的名称实际上是
of a big project which encapsulates a
一个包含一个
number of different features a number of
许多不同的功能
different bits of functionality so
功能各不相同
jigsaw includes breaking the JDK itself
拼图包括破坏JDK本身
into different individual modules it
分成不同的模块
includes things like the ability to
包括诸如
encapsulate these internal API is so
封装这些内部API就是这样
that you can so they can be hidden away
这样就可以将它们隐藏起来
so not only breaking the JDK into
所以不仅将JDK分为
modules but also taking things like the
模块，但也需要
Sun misc API well code and hiding that
Sun misc API良好的代码并将其隐藏
away so you can't see it anymore and
走开，所以你看不到它了，
then of course there's the module system
然后当然有模块系统
itself so they used the module system
本身，所以他们使用了模块系统
itself to to create the modular JDK and
自己来创建模块化的JDK和
this is also the thing that we're going
这也是我们要做的事情
to use in order to mod in order to add
使用为了mod为了添加
modularity to our own code the other
模块化我们自己的代码
thing that's under my project jigsaw is
我的项目拼图下的东西是
j-link which is the ability to is
j-link的能力是
they're having to apply deploy all of
他们必须申请部署所有
this whole massive thing that everything
这整个巨大的东西，一切
including Cobra and AWT and everything
包括眼镜蛇和AWT等
else you don't use along with your
否则你不会和你的一起使用
application J link will allow you to
应用程序J链接将允许您
pick up just the modules that you want
拿起你想要的模块
and deploy a much smaller profile of of
并部署较小的配置文件
Java for you to run your application on
Java，供您在以下位置运行应用程序
which can be super useful for keeping
这对于保持超级有用
costs down for improving deployment
降低部署成本
times and that sort of thing but mostly
时代之类的东西，但主要是
what people are thinking of when they
人们在想什么的时候
talk about jigsaw is they're talking
谈论拼图，他们在谈论
about the Java platform module system JP
关于Java平台模块系统JP
m/s itself so this is the thing that has
m / s本身，所以这就是
been added to Java to allow us to create
已添加到Java中以允许我们创建
modules in our in our code itself
我们代码本身中的模块
so I want to step through how I turned
所以我想逐步了解
my previous Java eight code into Java
我以前的Java 8代码变成了Java
nine modular code this was my original
九个模块化代码，这是我的原始代码
project structure as you can see I have
您可以看到我的项目结构
IntelliJ IDEA modules these bold things
IntelliJ IDEA模块将这些大胆的事情
are IntelliJ IDEA modules and an empty
是IntelliJ IDEA模块，一个为空
rod yep I'm sorry
是的，对不起
it seems this screen sharing is frozen
似乎此屏幕共享已冻结
can you check it what's what are you
你能检查一下你是什么吗
seeing at the moment there isn't well
眼下眼前不景气
worrying about the unsafe package okay
担心包裹不安全好吗
oh that's a while back then and that's
哦那是一段时间了
fine let me um let me try and fix that
好的，让我，让我尝试解决该问题
hold on a second can you see a slide
请稍等一下，您可以看到幻灯片吗
which says jigsaw yep
上面写着拼图
excellent okay so you haven't missed
很好，这样您就不会错过
that much that's fine and what I had I'm
那很好，我所拥有的
hoping you can't see my GoToWebinar
希望你看不到我的GoToWebinar
control panel
控制面板
I'm assuming that's hidden okay and when
我假设这是隐藏的，何时
I was talking about project jigsaw these
我当时在谈论项目拼图
are the different individual items that
是不同的个体项目
make up project jigsaw as I said there's
就像我说的那样编项目拼图
the modular JDK itself and capture that
模块化JDK本身并捕获
most internal API is J link to allow you
大多数内部API是J链接，允许您
to create a much smaller version of Java
创建一个小得多的Java版本
to deploy and and the module system
部署和模块系统
itself so we're going to look at the
本身，所以我们要看一下
module system itself
模块系统本身
here is the package package structure of
这是包装的包装结构
the the of my previous application this
我以前的应用程序的
is when I was running it under Java
是我在Java下运行它的时候
eight and you can see I've got IntelliJ
八个，你会看到我有IntelliJ
IDEA modules here I've got a dashboard
我这里有一个IDEA模块仪表板
I've got a service module which is
我有一个服务模块
reusable infrastructure code which
可重用的基础架构代码
should be used by all of my services and
我所有的服务都应该使用
then I have everything else and for some
然后我拥有其他一切
reason this made sense to me when I was
这对我来说很有意义
creating this application but in actual
创建此应用程序，但实际上
fact this doesn't really make quite as
事实上，这并不能使
much sense as I thought because I
就像我想的那样，因为我
actually have three back-end services
实际上有三个后端服务
which implies I should have three
这意味着我应该有三个
modules for those three independent
这三个独立的模块
pieces of code if I put them all into a
如果我将它们全部放入一个
single module they can be dependent upon
他们可以依赖的单个模块
each other in terms of code and they
彼此在代码方面，他们
shouldn't be so when I decided to apply
当我决定申请时不应该这样
the J PMS to my existing code I broke it
我现有的代码的J PMS我打破了它
up into into a much larger number of
变成更多的
modules so I still have my UI module I
模块，所以我仍然有我的UI模块
still have my service module with
仍然有我的服务模块
infrastructure code I have a new module
基础结构代码我有一个新模块
with some stuff around my reactive API
与我的反应式API有关的一些东西
and then I have three individual modules
然后我有三个单独的模块
for my three individual services which
为我的三个个人服务
makes a lot more sense the other thing
使另一件事更有意义
you might notice is that each of my
您可能会注意到，我的每一个
modules has a module - info Java file
模块有一个模块-信息Java文件
and this is how we tell the JVM that
这就是我们告诉JVM的方式
this is going to be using the the Java
这将使用Java
platform module system and that this
平台模块系统
this is basically our module descriptor
这基本上是我们的模块描述符
this is what our module is what it needs
这就是我们的模块所需要的
and what it exposes to the rest of the
以及它暴露给其余的
world if you look at demos and samples
如果您观看演示和样本，就会发现世界
and stuff you might see some tutorials
还有一些您可能会看到的教程
suggest that you have a structure which
建议你有一个结构
looks like this which has got a source
看起来像这样有一个来源
at the top and then a series of modules
在顶部，然后是一系列模块
inside and then a test at the top and a
内部，然后在顶部进行测试，
series of modules inside that that's the
里面的一系列模块
open JDK structure and we don't have to
打开JDK结构，我们不必
do that we can use a more grey verdant
这样做，我们可以使用更灰色的翠绿
got a great little slash maven style way
有一个很棒的小斜杠行家风格
where we have module at the top which
我们在顶部的模块
contains the source directory in a test
包含测试中的源目录
directory it doesn't really matter which
目录并不重要
way around you do it as long as your
只要你
module info file is inside your source
模块信息文件位于您的源代码中
directory or the directory which you
目录或您所在的目录
declare as your source root then it will
声明为您的源根目录，然后它将
work you'll be fine
工作就好了
so let's take a look at what this module
让我们来看看这个模块
- info dr. Java file is it's kind of an
-信息博士Java文件是一种
odd structure of a name for a Java file
Java文件名的奇数结构
normally we have camel case with
通常我们有骆驼案
uppercase and we don't have hyphens in
大写，并且我们没有连字符
that's changed to the correct branch
更改为正确的分支
okay so you can see all my modules here
好吧，所以你可以在这里看到我所有的模块
I've got my UI module I've got my
我有我的UI模块，我有我的
service module and a bunch of others
服务模块和其他一些
some of these or have already been
其中一些或已经
turned into Java 9 modules I'm going to
变成了我要使用的Java 9模块
go through the process of turning this
经过这个过程
flow module into a Java 9 module if I
如果我将模块流到Java 9模块
build this at the moment in theory
在理论上建立这个
everything should compile correctly even
一切都应该正确编译
though I have some Java 9 modules for
虽然我有一些Java 9模块
the module info and some intelligent
模块信息和一些智能
muddles that haven't defined module info
尚未定义模块信息的混乱
everything should still work and play
一切都应该正常工作
nicely together regardless
不管在一起很好
which it does which is good news those a
这是个好消息
bit worried for a second there so we can
有点担心在那里，所以我们可以
use IntelliJ to create a new module info
使用IntelliJ创建新的模块信息
file IntelliJ wolf will by default take
IntelliJ wolf文件将默认使用
the name of the intelligent and use that
智能的名称并使用
as the name of your Java 9 module first
作为您的Java 9模块的名称
off without doing anything else for this
不做任何其他事情
file let's rebuild it and see what the
文件，让我们重建它，看看
impact is from rebuilding the project
影响来自重建项目
now I have a modular file
现在我有一个模块化文件
now what happens now is we get a load of
现在发生了什么
compiler errors and this might seem kind
编译器错误，这似乎有点
of weird because we had a project which
之所以怪异，是因为我们有一个项目
was working perfectly acceptable and now
工作完全可以接受，现在
all we've done is added a single file
我们要做的就是添加一个文件
and suddenly things don't compile
突然间事情没有编译
properly but there's a fairly rational
适当，但有一个相当合理的
explanation for this of course as you'd
您当然会对此进行解释
expect in them let's go back to our
期待他们，让我们回到我们的
module info file by default module info
默认情况下，模块信息文件模块信息
files have this concept of importing
文件具有导入的概念
Java base ok so this says anything in
Java基础好，所以这说了什么
Java top base I get access to for free I
Java最基础的我可以免费使用
don't actually have to say that in my
其实我不必这么说
module info file I will get access to
模块信息文件，我将可以访问
that for free and the stuff that's in
那是免费的，里面的东西
there is things like Java dot util Java
有些东西像Java dot util Java
yang and the stuff that we kind of are
杨和我们喜欢的东西是
bound to use things like string you know
一定要使用诸如字符串之类的东西
all these things that which are really
所有这些真的是
important for us to use in day-to-day
对于我们日常使用很重要
programming but that's just the very
编程，但这仅仅是
very basic things that we need from the
我们需要的非常基本的东西
JDK so if we want to use anything else
JDK，所以如果我们想使用其他任何东西
than we need to say well we want to use
比我们要说的要好
the module that contains those things in
包含这些内容的模块
this case I'm using logging so I need to
在这种情况下，我正在使用日志记录，所以我需要
use the module Java dot logging in order
按顺序使用模块Java点记录
to in order to be able to use the logger
为了能够使用记录仪
so I use IntelliJ to do a quick fix for
所以我用IntelliJ快速修复
this if I go back to my module info I
如果我回到我的模块信息我
get requires Java logging and if we look
获取需要Java日志记录，如果我们看
at this let's drill into it
在此让我们深入研究
we can see now that the Java 9 JDK serve
我们现在可以看到Java 9 JDK
just been broken down into packages is
刚分解成包装是
broken down into modules and each of
分为模块，每个
these modules has packages inside it so
这些模块内部都有软件包，因此
what we've this the Javadoc basis
我们基于Javadoc的基础
obviously the stuff that we get by
显然我们得到的东西
default and i've just said i also want
默认，我只是说我也想要
to be able to use Javadoc logging which
能够使用Javadoc日志记录
gives me access to Java util logging so
使我可以访问Java util日志，因此
that's one error fixed let's go to
这是一个已解决的错误，让我们去
another error there's one more thing
另一个错误还有另外一件事
here which says object reactive streams
这里说对象反应流
is declared in module reactive dot
在模块反应性点中声明
streams but flow does not use it so I
流，但流量不使用它，所以我
also need to do this for external
外部也需要这样做
libraries as well obviously I'll just
图书馆显然我也只是
get IntelliJ to fix it for me because
让IntelliJ为我修复它，因为
I'm lazy like that and if we go into
我很懒，如果我们进入
module info now it says requires
现在说模块信息要求
reactive dot streams and this might seem
反应性点流，这似乎
kind of weird because the question is
有点奇怪，因为问题是
where did this come from this is clearly
这是从哪里来的？
not in the JDK because it doesn't start
不在JDK中，因为它没有启动
with Java or Java acts for start so
与Java或Java一起开始
where did this module come from and if I
这个模块是从哪里来的，如果我
drill into it this is an external jar
钻进去，这是一个外部罐子
file reactive - streams - 1 dot 0 dot 0
文件反应-流-1点0点0
dot jar what Java 9 does is it takes
dot jar Java 9要做的是
external jar files it strips off any
外部的jar文件会剥离任何
version number on the end turns things
最终版本号变成事情
like hyphens underscores to dots and
像连字号强调点和
then uses that as the module name and
然后将其用作模块名称，
then this is something called an
那就是所谓的
automatic module so things like external
自动模块，例如外部
jar files are kind of treated like they
jar文件就像对待它们一样
were modules even if they don't use Java
是模块，即使它们不使用Java
9 even if they don't have a module -
9即使他们没有模块-
info file in even if they're not truly
信息文件，即使它们不是真正的
modular they're treated as automatic
模块化，它们被视为自动
modules which allows us to migrate our
允许我们迁移我们的模块
code - using the Java module system
代码-使用Java模块系统
without being dependent upon everyone
不依赖所有人
else having done the same thing as well
否则也做同样的事情
one of the nice things that got
一件不错的事情
introduced in the late stages of Java 9
在Java 9后期引入
is these module names need to be unique
这些模块名称需要唯一吗
and library developers can declare in in
库开发人员可以在
their manifest they can declare what
他们的清单，他们可以宣布什么
their module name would be if they were
他们的模块名称将是
using Java 9 so it might be that it's
使用Java 9，因此可能是
not the Java on there which is good
不是那里的Java好
because we know sometimes Jaafar names
因为我们有时知道贾法尔的名字
can be creative some of the library
可以创意一些图书馆
developers may choose to tag their jar
开发人员可以选择标记他们的罐子
file with a module name so that's that
具有模块名称的文件，就是这样
that allows us to migrate gradually
让我们逐渐迁移
towards using Java 9 modules so now if I
使用Java 9模块，所以现在如果我
rebuild this let's see what happens
重建这个让我们看看会发生什么
this is all working but what happens if
一切正常，但是如果发生
I want to use any code from inside my
我想使用我内部的任何代码
flow module well let's try using it from
流模块，让我们尝试从中使用它
inside my user module let's do the same
在我的用户模块中，让我们做同样的事情
thing let's create our module info
让我们创建我们的模块信息
let's fix up the errors that we have I'm
让我们修复我所遇到的错误
just going to add these things to the
只是将这些东西添加到
module info so then you'll see that this
模块信息，那么您将看到
one has a very similar sort of setup to
一个具有非常相似的设置
the other one that we just created and
我们刚创建的另一个
then this one says package then stop
然后这个说包裹然后停止
flow is declared in module send stop
流程在模块发送停止中声明
flow which does not export it to module
不会将其导出到模块的流程
sensitive user I want to see if there's
敏感的用户，我想看看是否有
a quick fix on this anothers and so
快速解决这个问题
what this means is I know where this
这意味着我知道这在哪里
package is I know where the class is I
包是我知道我在哪里
know which module it lives in but that
知道它所在的模块，但是
module hasn't allowed me access to that
模块不允许我访问该模块
class so you can't use it so what I need
类，所以你不能使用它，所以我需要
to do is in here I need to say which
我要做的是在这里说
packages I allow people to use so I'm
我允许人们使用的软件包，所以我
going to export flow I want people to be
要出口流量我希望人们成为
able to use everything that's inside my
能够使用我内心的一切
flow package that's that's my public API
这是我的公共API的流程包
for my module note that if I have an
对于我的模块，请注意，如果我有一个
input package then I can keep that
输入包，然后我可以保留
secret and private and no one else can
秘密和私人的，没有其他人可以
use my import probe in my import package
在导入包中使用导入探针
and this surprised to reflection as well
这也让思考感到惊讶
as so people can't even reflect over my
这样人们甚至无法反省我
code they can't use it at all if I
代码他们根本无法使用
haven't exposed it so I can say I export
还没有暴露出来，所以我可以说我出口了
this package or I can even be more
这个包，我什至可以更多
specific than that and I can say I
比那具体，我可以说我
export it to a specific module so I
将其导出到特定模块，所以我
export it to user only only the user
仅将其导出给用户
module can use my flow module for
模块可以将我的流量模块用于
example if that's what I wanted to do
例如，如果这就是我想要做的
and if I want to allow people to reflect
如果我想让人们反思
over my code then I have to open it so I
在我的代码上然后我必须打开它，所以我
can open my editor a package level again
可以再次打开我的编辑器的包装级别
I can either open it to everyone to be
我可以向所有人开放
able to use reflection or I can say I
能够使用反射，或者我可以说我
open it to again some module to be able
再次将其打开到某个模块即可
to reflect over it and this is the power
反思它，这就是力量
of jigsaw not only do you get the
的拼图不仅可以
ability to separate your code into
可以将您的代码分成
individual modules and individual pieces
单个模块和单个零件
but you get a lot of control over what's
但是你对什么有很多控制
visible and what's not visible which
可见和不可见的
gives you obviously better design but
给您明显更好的设计，但
also better security as well so let's
更好的安全性，所以让我们
rebuild that and see what happens
重建它，看看会发生什么
let's go back to our user service so now
让我们回到我们的用户服务
I use the service all we have to do is
我使用的服务就是
say that we're going to use the flow
说我们将使用流程
module and then everything will work so
模块，然后一切都会正常工作
that's a quick intro to applying
这是申请的快速介绍
modularity Java 9 modularity to your
模块化Java 9对您的模块化
existing code you need a module info
现有代码，您需要模块信息
file you need to declare which modules
文件，您需要声明哪些模块
you're dependent on whether they are JDK
您取决于他们是否为JDK
modules whether they are our automatic
模块是否是我们的自动模块
modules ie these external jar files or
模块，即这些外部jar文件或
in the case of the user service you
对于用户服务，您
might be but you might be requiring one
可能是，但您可能需要一个
of your own modules and you also need to
自己的模块，还需要
be able to declare which packages you
能够声明您使用哪些软件包
allow people to see so in the case of my
让人们看到我的情况
user service for example I don't let
用户服务，例如，我不让
anyone else see anything in there
其他人在那里看到任何东西
because that's just a standalone service
因为那只是一个独立的服务
doesn't have any code that I want anyone
没有任何我想要的代码
else to be able to talk to in a slightly
其他的可以稍微谈一下
more complicated example or well I'll
更复杂的例子，或者我会
come back to that in a minute let me
请稍后再说
switch branches so I can show you a more
切换分支，以便我向您展示更多
complicated example so a slightly more
复杂的例子，所以稍微多一点
complicated example is is this one here
复杂的例子是这个吗
this is my UI code so my UI code
这是我的用户界面代码，所以我的用户界面代码
obviously I require Java FX modules from
显然我需要从
the JDK itself and what I actually need
JDK本身以及我实际需要的
to do is I need to open up my code to
要做的是我需要打开我的代码
reflection because the FX ml
反射，因为FX毫升
functionality uses reflection to to
功能使用反射来
basically to work basically between my
基本上在我之间工作
Java classes and my FX ml classes so
Java类和我的FX ml类如此
it's a slightly more complicated module
这是一个稍微复杂的模块
but you can see here the sort of
但您可以在这里看到
features that you're you're expecting to
您期望的功能
to use to create this particular module
用于创建此特定模块
info file
信息文件
I used brute force trial and error using
我使用蛮力试验和错误使用
errors that came up in the IntelliJ IDEA
IntelliJ IDEA中出现的错误
IDE and also runtime errors that happens
IDE以及发生的运行时错误
when I was trying to run things I do not
当我尝试运行事物时，我不会
recommend using brute force trial and
建议使用蛮力试用版，
error to create your module info file it
创建模块信息文件时出错
took me a couple of days
花了我几天
and even then it wasn't ID and it wasn't
即使那样，它也不是ID，也不是
it wasn't great the best thing to do is
最好的事情是
get to understand the tool called Jade
了解称为Jade的工具
EPS which will allow you will analyze
EPS将使您能够进行分析
the dependencies in your code and will
您代码中的依赖项，并将
tell you which modules you're using and
告诉您正在使用的模块，以及
therefore it will allow you to to create
因此，它将允许您创建
this module info file much more easily
该模块信息文件更容易
and much more neatly in the link that
在链接中更整洁地
I'll post at the end of the presentation
我将在演示文稿的末尾发布
there'll be some documentation if you
如果您有一些文档
follow that link there'll be some
跟随那个链接，会有一些
documentation like Jade EPS and how it
Jade EPS之类的文档以及如何使用
works so that's a really quick tour of
可以使您快速浏览
how to apply modularity to existing Java
如何将模块化应用于现有的Java
code in terms of the pain you might end
根据您可能会遭受的痛苦编写代码
up reorganizing the structure of your
重新组织您的结构
code jigsaw doesn't require it but you
代码拼图不需要，但是您
might find that when you're thinking in
在思考时可能会发现
terms of these modules these independent
这些模块的条款这些独立
pieces of code that you might want to
您可能想要的几段代码
separate your code a bit more like I did
像我一样分离您的代码
I wanted to create three separate
我想创建三个单独的
modules for my three separate services
我的三个独立服务的模块
so obviously structural reorganization
显然是结构重组
of of an application is non-trivial the
的应用程序是不平凡的
IDE support is obviously getting there
IDE支持显然已经实现
the last four or five versions of
的最后四个或五个版本
IntelliJ IDEA have incrementally added
IntelliJ IDEA已增量添加
more support for Java 9 features in
进一步支持Java 9功能
general and jigsaw features specifically
一般和拼图功能
but obviously this sort of thing takes
但是显然这种事情需要
time so you don't get quick fixes for
时间，所以您不会快速解决
absolutely everything however you did
绝对是您所做的一切
see that I can create my module info
看到我可以创建我的模块信息
file I can i've got quick fixes for
我可以快速修复的文件
adding the required statements to it I
在其中添加所需的语句
have I have code completion and
我有代码补全和
highlighting and a lot of the stuff that
突出显示的很多东西
I expect to be able to get while using
我希望能够在使用时得到
while working with any sort of Java file
在处理任何类型的Java文件时
so so yes so it works but it's not it's
所以是的，所以它可以工作，但是不是
not like you can say to IntelliJ create
不像你可以说要创建IntelliJ
my module info and have everything work
我的模块信息，一切正常
for you if you are going to use
如果您要使用的话
modularity do go and read the
模块化确实去阅读
documentation do go and find out what it
文档去看看它是什么
means what the implications are find out
意味着发现了什么含义
about Jade EPS and how it works because
关于Jade EPS及其工作原理，因为
it's it's a very big change to the
这是对我的很大改变
language it's one of the reasons why it
语言，这是为什么它的原因之一
took so long to create and to release
创建和发布花了很长时间
Java 9 and it's it has other
Java 9以及其他
implications which we haven't really
我们还没有真正的含义
covered like for example with jigsaw
像拼图一样覆盖
when you're using the Java platform
当您使用Java平台时
module system you're actually using a
您实际使用的模块系统
module path not a class path so that's
模块路径不是类路径，所以
quite a big change for class path you
您上课的路径有很大的改变
just put Java files on the class path
只需将Java文件放在类路径中
and you end up with this big bucket of
而你最终得到了一大桶
classes which gets paused in some
在某些课程中暂停的课程
arbitrary order and you can end up with
任意顺序，您最终可以
all sorts of weird problems in terms of
各种奇怪的问题
having duplicate classes in terms of
在以下方面有重复的课程
having version class crashes in terms of
版本类在以下方面崩溃
the performance of trying to pass this
试图通过这个的表现
class path and one of the things that
课堂路径和其中的一件事
jigsaw is supposed to solve is by
拼图应该解决的是
getting rid of class path and using
摆脱类路径并使用
module path it's much stricter in terms
模块路径，在术语上要严格得多
of what you're allowed to depend upon it
被允许依赖的东西
can do some analysis over do you have
可以对你有一些分析
two versions of the same class you're
您是同一班的两个版本
not allowed to do that
不允许这样做
do you have packages which appear in
你有出现在
more than one module you're not allowed
不允许使用多个模块
to have that either
拥有
do you have modules with non unique
你有非唯一的模块吗
names then these things are all
这些东西都是名字
restricted but that means that you can
受限制，但这意味着您可以
find some of the common errors like
找到一些常见的错误，例如
method not found problems for example
方法未发现问题
you can find common errors that would
您会发现常见错误，
lead to that when you start your
导致当你开始你的
application up not during one time so
申请没有一次，所以
you get the tricks allows you to fail
你懂的把戏会让你失败
faster it gives you errors up front
更快地给您带来错误
rather than having runtime errors so
而不是运行时错误
it's really important to understand the
了解这一点非常重要
full implications of using the of using
使用的全部含义
the job module system which means if
作业模块系统，这意味着
you're interested in using it do go and
你有兴趣使用它去
read all the documentation and there's
阅读所有文档，然后
plenty in the spensive great books too
大量的精彩书籍中也有
and the game obviously you get cleaner
游戏显然会变得更清洁
design I mean we were probably quoting
设计我的意思是我们可能会引用
module assistance anyway you can use
无论如何都可以使用模块帮助
IntelliJ ideas modules obviously or
IntelliJ想法模块显然或
Gradle or maven to create modular design
Gradle或Maven创建模块化设计
OSGi there's a lot of different
OSGi有很多不同
solutions out there but thinking about
解决方案，但思考
modules as a sort of first-class citizen
作为一流公民的模块
of the language leads you in my
语言的引导您进入我的
experience it leads you to have better
体验它会使你变得更好
encapsulation better separation of
包封更好的分离
concerns better object-oriented design
关注更好的面向对象设计
this is a good thing reliable
这是一件可靠的好事
configuration like I said the removal of
像我说的删除配置
the class path and moving towards module
上课的道路并走向模块
path means that you can get some of
路径意味着您可以得到一些
these common errors you get them upfront
这些常见错误可以使您提前
so you can fix them well before they end
这样您就可以在结束之前修复好它们
up in production this is definitely a
在生产中肯定是一个
good thing
好东西
and smaller deployables so I mentioned
和较小的可部署项目，所以我提到
this when I talked about j-link the the
当我谈论j-link时
point here is that now we're in a
这里的意思是，现在我们在
modular world we can pick and choose
我们可以选择的模块化世界
which modules who want to deploy and we
谁想部署哪些模块，我们
can bundle all of those up just the
可以将所有这些捆绑在一起
modules we want and deploy them into the
我们想要的模块并将其部署到
cloud or answer an internet things
云或回答互联网的事情
device or wherever we want to and we can
设备或我们想要的任何地方，我们可以
have a much smaller footprint of our
在我们的足迹较小
applications which is definitely a good
应用程序绝对是一个很好的
thing well let's move on really and
好吧，让我们继续前进，
really quickly cover the reactive API
真的很快涵盖了反应式API
because this is now part of Java 9 and I
因为这现在是Java 9和我的一部分
think that's an interesting thing to at
认为这是一件有趣的事情
least be aware of there's a mature
至少要注意有一个成熟的
stable reactor streams API which comes
稳定的反应器物流API
under org dot reactive streams it has a
在组织点反应流下，它有一个
publisher a subscriber a processor which
向订户发布处理器
combines the publisher and the
结合了出版商和
subscriber and a subscription and this
订户和订阅以及此
is kind of the core basic building
是核心的基础建筑
blocks of a lot of the reactive
很多反应堆
libraries and is implemented by things
库并由事物实现
like occur rx Java vertex reactor a lot
就像发生了很多Java顶点反应器一样
of the common reactive libraries so
常见的反应库
what's interesting about this is it's
有趣的是
stable enough and accepted enough that
足够稳定并足够接受
it's now part of the Java 9 layer of
现在它已成为Java 9层的一部分
Java 9 of the language itself is under
Java 9语言本身
Java dot util co-current and it's under
Java dot util并发并且在
flow and it looks the same as the
流，它看起来与
reactive streams API it is important to
反应流API对
notice though that it's not exactly the
注意，虽然这不完全是
same because it's in a different package
相同，因为它在不同的包装中
and it has a different structure so
它具有不同的结构，所以
out-of-the-box rxjava
开箱即用的rxjava
for example is not going to be exposing
例如不会被曝光
the java 9 flow api because it's using
Java 9 Flow api，因为它正在使用
the org reactive streams 1 however you
组织反应流1但是您
can either use adaptors to move between
可以使用适配器在两个之间移动
the two in the meantime but I've also
在此期间的两个，但我也
seen a number of the libraries that
看到了一些图书馆，
implement reactive streams like akka and
实施反应式流，例如akka和
like reactor have and started to move
像反应堆一样，并开始移动
towards using the java 9 api so I think
对使用Java 9 API的想法
this is really interesting because it
这真的很有趣，因为它
means that reactive programming has
意味着反应式编程具有
become really quite accepted if it's
如果真的变得很被接受
actually part of Java the language it
实际上是Java语言的一部分
means that these reactive libraries can
意味着这些反应性库可以
be talking to each other using the same
用相同的方式互相交谈
API which is part of the the core jdk
API是核心jdk的一部分
itself and i do have a lot of examples
本身和我确实有很多例子
of using this and how it impacts
使用它的方式及其影响
the architecture of your application but
应用程序的架构，但是
I'm not going to go into that in this
我不会在这方面
particular presentation but you can see
特定的演示文稿，但您可以看到
a copy of that again in the link at the
该链接的副本再次位于
end of this presentation there's some
在本演讲结束时，有一些
videos of that stuff as well if you are
这些东西的视频，如果你是
interested specifically in the reactive
对反应性特别感兴趣
programming side of things okay that
编程方面还可以
means we've got half an hour or probably
意味着我们有半个小时甚至可能
slightly less if we want time for
如果我们想花点时间
questions to go over all the other
其他所有问题
features in Java 9 which might sound
Java 9中的功能可能听起来不错
like plenty of time but it quite
喜欢很多时间，但是
frequently is not there's quite a lot of
经常没有很多
stuff in Java that oh actually let's
哦，实际上让我们
pause right now and see if there are any
现在暂停，看看是否有任何
burning questions that need answering
燃烧需要回答的问题
before we move on to this Andray okay a
在我们继续这个Andray之前，好吧
call so we have a couple of questions so
打电话，所以我们有几个问题，所以
first question is there maven support
第一个问题是是否有Maven支持
for modules using the standard maven
对于使用标准Maven的模块
folder structure like source main Java
类似于源主Java的文件夹结构
and so soil and so forth yes so there's
所以土壤等等，所以有
this kind of two questions there if you
如果您有两个这样的问题
use the classic maven slash Gradle
使用经典的Maven斜杠Gradle
structure of source main Java will that
源主Java的结构将表明
work with modules yes I have used that
使用模块是的，我已经用过了
that works fine too does maven work with
也可以正常工作的行家
Java 9 yes maven has worked with Java 9
Java 9是，Maven已使用Java 9
for quite a while now and so it
现在已经有一段时间了
definitely works I've used it myself and
绝对有效，我自己使用过，
it works fine and Gradle also works with
它工作正常，Gradle也可以使用
Java 9 since Gradle 4.1 and so the build
Java 9自Gradle 4.1以来的构建
systems are working with Java 9 now
系统现在正在使用Java 9
including including fully embracing
包括完全拥抱
modularity so if you have a module info
模块化，因此如果您有模块信息
file you can build that with Gradle or
您可以使用Gradle或
with made the next question can you use
下一个问题可以用吗
the new model system for creating
用于创建的新模型系统
Android applications in future
未来的Android应用程序
theoretically in future yes but Android
从理论上讲，是的，但Android
still Java 6 right ish but it androids
仍然是Java 6，但它是androids
moving to the open JDK so there's no
转移到开放的JDK，所以没有
reason why it can't adopt all of the
为什么不能采用所有
same features which are coming in Java 9
Java 9中即将出现的相同功能
which went into the open JDK could
进入开放的JDK可以
eventually go into Android as well
最终也进入了Android
yeah so basically we don't know yet we
是的，所以基本上我们还不知道
don't know yeah but there's no reason
不知道是的，但是没有理由
why not
为什么不
basically yep so then do you plan to
是的，所以你打算
clarify the situation about using
澄清使用情况
libraries without module info for
没有模块信息的库
example about using Google AdWords API
有关使用Google AdWords API的示例
using libraries without much of in fact
实际上没有太多使用图书馆
so this is basically automatic modules
所以这基本上是自动模块
as far as I understand it automatic
据我了解自动
modules Oh what I wanted to do actually
模块哦，我实际上想做什么
is I wanted to show let me show you
我想展示让我展示给你吗
quickly the the module diagram and
快速的模块图和
IntelliJ IDEA I the reason being I hope
我希望IntelliJ IDEA
this will answer this question
这将回答这个问题
if it doesn't and I will try again so
如果没有，我会再试一次
this is a visualization of the modules
这是模块的可视化
that you're using so I'm using this is
您正在使用，所以我正在使用的是
my client module I'm using my back-end
我的客户端模块我正在使用我的后端
service module the client module uses a
客户端模块使用的服务模块
bunch of JDK modules all shown in yellow
一堆JDK模块全部显示为黄色
and the service module uses a lot of
服务模块使用了很多
blue external libraries so these are not
蓝色的外部库，所以这些不是
these don't have module infos in they
这些没有模块信息
are not proper modules they're automatic
不是正确的模块，它们是自动的
modules they're just external jar files
模块只是外部jar文件
so this works and the point is that your
所以这行得通，关键是你的
application can carry on using the same
应用程序可以使用相同的
jar file as it was using before and
之前和之前使用的jar文件
pretending that they are modules even if
假装它们是模块，即使
you convert yourself to being a fully
你把自己变成了一个完全
modular project there are some risks
模块化项目存在一定风险
around this however because there are I
围绕这个但是因为有我
mean as I mentioned things like the Java
就像我提到Java之类的意思
platform module system doesn't allow you
平台模块系统不允许您
to have things like the same package in
具有类似的包装
multiple jar files there are
有多个jar文件
restrictions on the way you structure
对您的结构方式的限制
your code that weren't that weren't
您的代码不是，不是
there in earlier versions of Java so not
Java的早期版本中没有
all earlier versions of jar files for
的所有早期版本的jar文件
example are going to play that nicely
例子会很好玩
with with the module system a lot of
与模块系统一起
common libraries do for example I've
常见的库例如
been reading that hibernate works fine
一直在阅读休眠状态很好
and that's like I said maven and Gradle
就像我说的Maven和Gradle
works fine spring works fine there's a
春季很好，作品很好
bunch of stuff that just works fine with
一堆很好用的东西
job and I'm without you having to
工作，我不用你
do anything but some some libraries
除了一些图书馆以外什么都不做
might not so I guess my short answer is
可能不会，所以我想我的简短答案是
if you're using automatic modules and
如果您使用的是自动模块，
these sharpers blue on these diagrams it
这些图表上的这些锐利的蓝色
should work fine with Java nine
应该与Java 9正常工作
automatic modules have been designed
设计了自动模块
from Java nine point of view to be very
从Java的九个角度来看非常
flexible around how the code works
围绕代码的工作方式灵活
because it's understood that the code in
因为我们了解其中的代码
those libraries is not Java nine ready
那些库不是Java九就绪的
but you may find that some libraries
但您可能会发现一些图书馆
don't play that nicely because because
表现不好，因为
of the new restrictions placed on them
对他们施加的新限制
by Java nine does that answer the
Java 9可以回答
question
题
yep I think it does next question how
是的，我认为接下来的问题是
can we found all unsupported packages
我们可以找到所有不受支持的软件包吗
like you you were you were showing the
就像你一样，你正在展示
warning by the idea about the unsafe
警告关于不安全的想法
package import statement so you use this
包导入语句，以便您使用此
tool called Jade EPS I'm I don't really
我叫Jade EPS的工具
have a lot of time to go over it but
有很多时间来解决它，但是
let's have a look at it Jade F sharp
让我们来看看Jade F Sharp
nine and
九和
and actually the Oracle blog does a good
实际上，Oracle博客做得很好
job of this anyway it's in
无论如何，这是在
there's a link to a tutorial in there
那里有一个教程的链接
and but if I look at the reference
但是如果我看参考
documentation it's in Java 8 and in Java
Java 8和Java中的文档
night
晚
that's not your jaidev's there we go
那不是你的杰伊德夫我们在那里
there's a link to this at the end of the
在结尾处有一个与此相关的链接
sides anyway so what you do is that it
无论如何，所以你要做的是
does a bunch of different things you can
可以做很多不同的事情
use Jade EPS in java 8 against you Java
在Java 8中对Java使用Jade EPS
8 code and it will tell you it will warn
8个代码，它将告诉您它将警告
you about any dependencies that you're
关于您所依赖的任何内容
not supposed to be using like Sun disk
不应该像Sun磁盘那样使用
you can use Jade EPS in your Java 9 code
您可以在Java 9代码中使用Jade EPS
to see what your module dependencies are
看看你的模块依赖是什么
to help you build up your module info so
帮助您建立模块信息，以便
it's worth getting to understand what
值得了解什么
this tool does because it will make your
该工具会这样做，因为它将使您
life a lot easier if you can understand
如果您能理解，生活就会轻松很多
how to use it and it's it's non-trivial
如何使用它是不平凡的
using it but there's quite a few
使用它，但有很多
examples of how to use it out there ok
如何在那里使用它的例子好
cool then the module needs to be named
很酷，那么模块需要命名
the same as package name it doesn't need
与不需要的包名称相同
to the the suggestion is that it will
的建议是，它将
follow reverse DNS the same as package
按照反向DNS与软件包相同
names too that is the suggestions it
名字也就是建议
doesn't have to be called the same thing
不必被称为同一件事
as the package but it could be called
作为包装，但可以称为
the same thing as your as your artifact
和你的神器一样
if you like as you can see this doesn't
如果您喜欢，您可以看到这并不
apply to automatic modules because they
适用于自动模块，因为它们
were using the jar file name but the
使用的是jar文件名，但是
suggestion has been to use reverse dns
建议一直使用反向DNS
for your package names and I think this
您的包裹名称，我认为这
is to help you create an unique module
是为了帮助您创建一个独特的模块
names
名字
you
您
okay so we moving on with the questions
好的，所以我们继续讨论问题
in Java 9 to take advantage of jigsaw is
在Java 9中利用拼图是
it recommended to require that packages
它建议要求该软件包
are contained in the single module on
包含在单个模块上
your sorry
你对不起
yes jigsaw module um is it required the
是的拼图模块，是否需要
packages are in a single module
包在一个模块中
don't quite understand the question
不太明白这个问题
sorry yeah but maybe we can comment on
对不起，但也许我们可以发表评论
that that in one module you you may have
在一个模块中您可能拥有的
several packages and there's the only
几个包，只有一个
constraint right so for example my
约束权利，例如我的
client module has multiple packages and
客户端模块具有多个软件包，并且
I can choose to expose as as few or as
我可以选择少曝光或少曝光
many of those as I want my mood module
许多我想要的情绪模块
just has one package which is sensed
只有一个被感知的包裹
mood and again I can choose to expose as
心情，我可以再次选择暴露为
many as few as I want what I can't do is
我想要的只有很少的我不能做的是
I can't have in let's say in my flow
我不能在流程中说
module I can't have a package called
模块我不能有一个叫做
sense top mood because sense that mood
感觉最好的心情，因为感觉到那种心情
is in my mood so I can have more than
在我的心情中，所以我可以拥有更多
one package in my in my module in this
我的模块中的一个包裹
case look I actually only export one I
案例看，我实际上只导出一个我
export my client package I don't export
导出我不导出的客户程序包
any of my internal packages but I can
我的任何内部软件包，但我可以
have internal packages there and I could
有内部包装，我可以
have choose to expose one or more of
选择暴露一个或多个
them and I can have Erica have modules
他们，我可以让Erica有模块
which are just made up of one of one
只是其中之一
package
包
okay then is it correct that with
好吧，那是正确的
modules I have to type twice the package
我必须输入两次包装的模块
names once a module requires part the
一旦模块需要部分名称
other as imports part effectively yes in
其他作为进口有效一部分
that so let's have a look so my
所以让我们来看一下
dashboard for example I still have all
例如仪表板我仍然拥有所有
the standard imports I haven't changed
我没有改变的标准进口
any of that and I have import and I
任何一个，我都有进口，我
prefer to use my imports as individual
宁愿将我的进口商品作为个人使用
classes I don't group it in package
我没有将其分组的课程
level and then of course I have to also
水平，然后我当然也必须
say my module info that I require JavaFX
说出我需要JavaFX的模块信息
stock controls jar of X dot F F XML for
库存控件的X点FF XML罐
example so effectively but yes you have
这样的例子很有效，但是是的
to type it twice but as you know
键入两次，但如您所知
IntelliJ means that you don't have to do
IntelliJ意味着您不必做
much typing at all and again it's
一次又一次的打字
important to understand that here let's
重要的是要了解这里
go to dashboard again here we're talking
再次转到仪表板，我们正在谈论
about packages JavaFX to F XML JavaFX to
关于将JavaFX打包为F XML JavaFX到
application JavaFX Docs scene and but
应用程序JavaFX Docs的场景，但是
here we're talking about modules and
在这里，我们正在谈论模块和
modules actually have more than one
模块实际上有多个
packaging so if we have a look at this
包装，所以如果我们看看这个
one for example there are effects
例如有效果
controls oh well that just has seen in
控制好哦，刚刚在
it let's look at base then
然后让我们看一下基础
has JavaFX doc Bienstock collections to
具有JavaFX Doc Bienstock集合以
event on you till so i only need to
事件直到你，所以我只需要
include in my module info i only need to
在我的模块信息中包括我只需要
include the module level and then in my
包括模块级别，然后在我的
dashboard i have to include package
仪表板，我必须包括包装
level as as always as I always did so
一如既往地保持水平
next question if if there are were two
下一个问题，如果有两个
packages java.lang clogging java.util
软件包java.lang阻塞了java.util
logging how would I know which one I
记录我怎么知道我哪一个
require by by require Java logging in
通过按要求登录Java
module info Java so if you're using Java
模块信息Java，因此，如果您使用的是Java
logging let's have a look at this one
日志让我们看一看
only contains Java dot util dot logging
仅包含Java点util点记录
so it only has that one package in it
所以里面只有一个包裹
I'm assuming that the Sun is there is
我假设太阳在那里
internal stuff we should be looking at
我们应该关注的内部内容
so if I'm using Java dot util dot
所以如果我使用Java dot util dot
logging then I require the java dot
记录然后我需要Java点
logging module so if there's another
记录模块，所以如果还有另一个
logging which is worse if there was
如果有
another logging like log4j then I
另一个日志，如log4j然后我
wouldn't be using Java logging I'd be
不会使用Java日志记录
using them of blog for John module
使用博客的约翰模块
instead okay so there are already some
相反，好吧，所以已经有一些
people complaining about too many
人们抱怨太多
questions so let me know if you prefer
问题，让我知道你是否愿意
to know on and then yeah if if it's
要知道，然后如果是的话
possible we'll try to address questions
可能我们会尝试解决问题
with the follow-up email yes let's do
与后续电子邮件是的，让我们做
that let's do a let's do a blog post on
让我们做一个博客文章
the questions so we only have 15 minutes
问题，所以我们只有15分钟
left so keep asking the questions
离开所以继续问问题
through through the through GoToWebinar
通过GoToWebinar
and if we don't have time to get to the
如果我们没有时间去
questions we'll answer them on the blog
问题，我们将在博客上回答
because a lot of these questions are
因为这些问题很多
really good questions cool thanks all
真的很好的问题很酷谢谢大家
right let's move on to everything else
好的，让我们继续其他一切
in Chavan I
在Chavan I
convenience factory methods for
便利工厂方法
collections this is my favorite feature
收藏这是我最喜欢的功能
of Java 9 which which Mike it might seem
Java 9的代码，Mike可能看起来像
like a really silly thing but it really
像一个非常愚蠢的东西，但它确实
makes life an awful lot easier and I
使生活变得更加轻松，而我
think this is something that developers
认为这是开发商
are going to be using all the time let's
将一直使用，让我们
take a look at what this is so right now
看看这是怎么回事
what we'll find it in a lot of our code
我们会在很多代码中找到什么
when we're trying to create maybe a
当我们试图创建一个
static list we might be using it for
静态列表，我们可能会将其用于
tests we might be using a production
测试我们可能正在使用的产品
data as we probably use arrays as lists
数据，因为我们可能使用数组作为列表
and arrays as list gives us an array
和数组作为列表给我们一个数组
that we gives us a list that we can't
我们给我们一个清单，我们不能
add values to but what we don't always
增加价值，但我们并非总是如此
realize is that you can actually still
意识到你实际上仍然可以
change these values if you want to
如果您想更改这些值
probably what we wanted was an
可能我们想要的是
unmodifiable list but with the arrays as
不可修改的列表，但数组为
list I can say list get one and then set
我可以说列表得到一个然后设置
it to something different so usually
通常不同
what we really want is there as an
我们真正想要的是
unmodifiable list but we tend not to do
无法修改的清单，但我们倾向于不这样做
that because that's an awful lot of
那是因为那很多
typing but in Java 9 and as you can see
键入，但在Java 9中，如您所见
IntelliJ tells me I can use this this
IntelliJ告诉我我可以用这个
can now be replaced with a much smaller
现在可以替换为更小的
core all of that can be replaced with
核心全部可以替换为
lists of and this gives me an immutable
的列表，这给了我一个不变的东西
list so not only kind not append values
列出，因此不仅种类不附加值
to it I also can't change anything the
对此我也无法更改任何内容
implementation is subtly different to
实施与
the unmodifiable list but the
不可修改的清单，但
implications are the same it gives me a
含义是相同的，它给了我一个
list that I can't do anything with which
列出我对此无能为力
is good because it means we have control
很好，因为这意味着我们有控制权
over our data it's also good because
对我们的数据也很好，因为
it's easier for the JVM to reason over
JVM可以更容易地进行推理
and potentially optimize as well this is
并可能进行优化，这是
this is useful in terms of lists where
就列表而言，这很有用
it's really useful is in terms of some
这真的很有用
of the other data structures for example
例如其他数据结构
sets now sets never really had a very
现在的游戏机从未真正拥有过
nice way of creating a set so I have to
创建集合的好方法，所以我必须
values I want to put into my set and yet
我想放入设定中的值
I have to give it all of this
我必须把这一切都给
boilerplate just to create that set I
样板只是为了创建那个我
have to turn it into a list I have to
必须将其转换为清单
put in hash set and how to wrap that in
放入哈希集以及如何将其包装
a non modifiable set and or I can use
不可修改的集，或者我可以使用
set of this is going to be much easier
这一套会容易得多
for us this might help us start to use
对我们来说这可能有助于我们开始使用
the right data structures for the right
正确的数据结构
things because often we use lists
事情，因为我们经常使用列表
because it's just the easiest thing to
因为这只是最简单的事情
create so I think this is super useful
创建，所以我认为这超级有用
and you can also do the same thing a
你也可以做同样的事情
similar thing for the maps so this code
地图上也有类似的东西，所以这段代码
is again genuine coded night I had in my
再次是我在我的真实编码之夜
application I really did need to create
我确实需要创建的应用程序
a map a static map which Maps a string
映射字符串的静态映射
the value of some kind to a mood value
某种情绪的价值
of some kind and I have to put it inside
某种类型的，我必须把它放进去
a static look and it's kind of ugly and
静态的外观，有点丑陋，
I was never very happy about it but
我从未对此感到非常高兴，但
that's what you do in Java except that
那是您在Java中所做的，除了
now you can say Maps or of entries I can
现在您可以说地图或我可以输入的条目
use my favorites IntelliJ feature which
使用我最喜欢的IntelliJ功能
is column select mode let's put this
是列选择模式，让我们把它
down here we say map entry we use
在这里，我们说我们使用的地图条目
IntelliJ it is most used feature which
IntelliJ是最常用的功能
is Find and Replace let's replace all of
是查找并替换让我们替换所有
those
那些
get rid of column select and now we have
摆脱列选择，现在我们有了
our map of entries with strings to moods
我们的带有字符串到情绪的条目映射
it's a bit less boilerplate we got rid
少了一些样板，我们摆脱了
of our nasty static block here so that's
在这里我们讨厌的静态块
great
大
obviously if we use static imports then
显然，如果我们使用静态导入
we can make this a tiny bit even neater
我们可以使它更加整洁
so let's do that and that's that's quite
所以让我们做到这一点，那就是相当
nice that is a big improvement over what
很好，这是对什么的很大改进
we had before what's even better is if
我们曾经有过更好的选择是
we have fewer than ten entries we can do
我们可以完成的条目少于十个
something even simpler we can say map of
我们可以说更简单的地图
and then we can get rid of this we can
然后我们可以摆脱它，我们可以
get rid of this and we can have a
摆脱这个，我们可以有一个
compile error what I did wrong backed
编译错误我做错了什么
off I got too many yeah I had too many
我有太多，是的，我有太多
you have to you've got a minimum a
你必须至少有一个
maximum of ten that you did do so then
然后最多可以这样做十个
all I have to do is I just put key value
我要做的就是放关键值
pairs here a key value value value so
在这里将键值对值配对
I've just got rid of a lot of
我刚刚摆脱了很多
boilerplate that this can be really
样板，这真的可以
useful especially for test data but
特别适用于测试数据，但
might be really useful in production
在生产中可能真的有用
code too and obviously you get compiler
代码也很明显，您会得到编译器
errors if you don't fill in the the
错误，如果您不填写
right key value key value combination it
右键键值键值组合吗
gets a little bit more fluffy if your
如果您的身体变得蓬松一点
key and value are the same type in which
键和值是相同的类型
case I would recommend probably using
的情况下，我建议可能使用
the of entries version so you can group
条目版本的，因此您可以进行分组
together your key in your value so that
一起将您的钥匙变成您的价值，以便
you know that you haven't you haven't
你知道你没有你没有
accidentally done I don't know something
不小心做了我不知道的事
like this where one of those are
像这样，其中之一是
supposed to be key in one Swiss people a
应该是一个瑞士人的关键
so
所以
this will make our code a lot a lot
这将使我们的代码很多
nicer it's not quite as nice as saying
更好，不如说的好
something in a groovy style way but it's
以一种时髦的方式，但是
definitely a step in the right direction
绝对是朝正确方向迈出的一步
and I think this will make our code a
我认为这将使我们的代码成为
lot easier in the future I'm going to
以后我要轻松得多
roll that back so I don't get my
滚回去，所以我不明白我的意思
compiler error so yes that's convenience
编译器错误，是的，这很方便
factory methods for collections I just I
我只是我的工厂收集方法
really do want to get through these as
真的很想通过这些
fast as possible so I will try and show
尽可能快，所以我会尝试展示
them as quickly as possible
他们尽快
private methods and interfaces this
私有方法和接口
might seem very silly because your
可能看起来很傻，因为您的
interface is supposed to be your public
接口应该是您的公共
API so why would you need to put a
API，为什么要放一个
private method on your public API well I
我的公共API上的私有方法
will show you in Java eight interfaces
将以Java八个界面向您展示
got magic super powers in Java eight you
在Java 8中拥有神奇的超能力
can now have static methods and default
现在可以有静态方法和默认值
methods so your methods on interfaces
方法，所以接口上的方法
might actually have behavior and not
可能实际上有行为而没有
just their definition of your API which
只是他们对您API的定义
means that you can end up in this case
表示您可以在这种情况下结束
where I've got duplicate code between
我之间有重复的代码
these two methods and I can't really do
这两种方法我真的做不到
anything about that because if I extract
关于那件事，因为如果我提取
this into its own method let's call it
把它变成自己的方法，我们称之为
get value for field let's call that
获得领域的价值，我们称之为
field name
栏位名称
then what I've got is I have a new
然后我有一个新的
public method on my interface which is
我接口上的公共方法是
not what I wanted what I wanted was to
不是我想要的是
reshare the code between those two
在这两个之间共享代码
things without actually without exposing
事情实际上没有暴露
it to the end-users now in Java 9 it's
现在在Java 9中将其提供给最终用户
as simple as that's now private method
就像现在私有方法一样简单
so Java 9 has a lot of these small
所以Java 9有很多这些小功能
features which is just going to make
即将制作的功能
life a little bit easier for us as
生活对我们来说稍微容易一些
developers things that they probably
开发人员可能会做的事情
wanted to put in earlier versions of
想放入较早的版本
Java and but just didn't have time to do
Java，但没有时间做
it new methods on the streams API again
再次在流API上使用新方法
this is something that would have been
这本来是
nice in Java 8 but it's nice that we're
在Java 8中很不错，但是很高兴
getting it in Java 9 let's look at oh
在Java 9中获取它让我们看一下哦
while we're here let's have a look at
当我们在这里，让我们来看看
something one of the things that you can
你可以做的一件事情
get you can do now is now you can use
现在就可以使用了
effectively final or final values in try
尝试有效的最终值或最终值
with resources you might not have
有你可能没有的资源
realized that you can do this before but
意识到您可以做到这一点，但是
you can now do it in Java 9 and it's
您现在可以在Java 9中进行操作了
just a tiny improvement it's quite nice
只是一个很小的改进，这是非常好的
now Java 8 streams allow you to work
现在，Java 8流使您可以工作
with infinite streams this is cool this
与无限的流，这很酷
is great and theoretically awesome
在理论上很棒，很棒
except that if you're working with a
除了如果您正在使用
genuinely infinite stream in Java 8 it's
Java 8中的真正无限流是
very difficult to actually terminate
实际上很难终止
that infinite stream unless you put a
那无限的溪流，除非你把
limit on or or one of the few
限制或其中之一
terminating features in in Java 8
终止Java 8中的功能
streams now with Java 9 this becomes a
Java 9现在流
little bit easier now what this code
现在一点点容易什么这段代码
does is it reads all the lines from a
它是从一个读取所有行吗
file so the file contains Twitter
文件，因此文件包含Twitter
information and this gives me a stream
信息，这给了我一个信息流
where each value each string each value
其中每个值每个字符串每个值
in the stream is a line from the file
流中是文件中的一行
and what I might want to do is not
我可能想做的不是
infinite this it doesn't stop until you
无限，直到你，它不会停止
get to the end of the file I might want
到达我可能想要的文件末尾
to say take while let's say s is not
说拿，而说s不是
equal to some value let's say there's
等于一些价值，假设有
some secret superpower in there which
那里有一些秘密的超级大国
says I've reached the end of the file so
说我已经到达文件末尾，所以
let's process this stream until you hit
让我们处理此流，直到您点击
some value or let's assume this file
一些值，或者假设这个文件
let's assume that the strings in this
我们假设其中的字符串
file
文件
with a number and they're ordered so for
有一个数字，他们被订购以便
example you have like one two three four
例如你有一个一二三四
you've got hundreds start one and twenty
你有一百个开始一二十
to start with two so I might want to say
从两个开始，所以我可能想说
process this stream while s doesn't
处理此流，而s不处理
start with I don't know let's say number
首先我不知道说多少
three so I want to process everything
三个，所以我想处理一切
that starts with one everything that
从一切开始
starts with two and then stop when I get
从两个开始，然后在我得到时停止
to something that starts with three the
以三个开始的东西
flip side of this this is another method
反面这是另一种方法
called drop while which allows me to
叫滴而我可以
ignore everything up to some point so I
在某种程度上忽略一切
might want to ignore everything that
可能想忽略一切
starts with one for example so ignore
例如以一个开始，所以忽略
everything that starts with one process
一切始于一个过程
the next lot of stuff and then stop when
接下来的很多东西，然后停下来
you find something that starts at three
您会发现始于三点的东西
for example so and there's a number of
例如，有很多
different ways of using this but
不同的使用方式，但是
basically take while and drop while
基本上需要片刻，而片刻
allow you to to process infinite
允许您处理无限
infinite streams until some value is
无限流，直到某个值是
reached so I might want to say take
到达，所以我可能想说
while running is true and I could create
跑步时是真的，我可以创造
field running is true and then when stop
字段运行为真，然后停止
is called I could say running equals
被称为我可以说等于
false so process the stream while while
错误，因此在处理流的同时
you're running in real life of course
你当然在现实生活中奔跑
there should be an atomic boolean not a
应该有一个原子布尔而不是
boolean value etc but this is another
布尔值等，但这是另一个
thing you can do so now infinite streams
你现在可以做的事情无限流
are much more controllable in Java 9
在Java 9中更加可控
using take while and drop while
用一会儿而一会儿
similarly there's new methods and
同样，有新方法
optional this makes optional a little
可选，这使得可选一些
bit easier to work with as well so if
也会更容易使用，所以如果
you've been reading the the IntelliJ
您已经在阅读IntelliJ
blog you'll see that I was struggling a
博客，您会发现我在努力
little bit with how to make optional
一点如何使可选
effective in legacy code because in
在旧版代码中有效，因为
legacy code we do stuff with null values
旧代码，我们用空值填充
we probably should never have been doing
我们可能永远不应该做
in the first place but it was easy so we
首先，这很容易，所以我们
did it so let's take a look at an
做到了，所以让我们来看看
example of some of an optional
一些可选的例子
if you've been using optional in Java 8
如果您一直在Java 8中使用可选
you'll know let's extract this out so we
您会知道我们将其提取出来，所以我们
can have a look let's call this optional
可以看一下，我们将此称为可选
if you've been using optional in Java 8
如果您一直在Java 8中使用可选
you'll know that you can do things like
你会知道你可以做类似的事情
I want to say I want the value of
我想说我想要的价值
optional or some other default value or
可选或其他一些默认值或
go to this method and get me some
去这种方法，给我一些
default value or you can say or else
默认值，或者您可以说否则
throw an exception for example those are
抛出异常，例如那些是
kind of your three main things and what
你的三个主要方面是什么
they do is they will unwrap the optional
他们做的是，他们将打开可选的
and return you a mood object in this
并在此返回一个心情对象
case this is an optional of mode in Java
这种情况是Java模式的可选
9 you can just say or you'd and that
9你可以说或者你会说
returns you an optional of mood not the
返回给您一种可选的心情，而不是
unwrapped mood so let's say let me show
解开情绪，让我说出
you an example of this so get
你一个这样的例子
alternative optional value I'll just put
我将输入另一个可选值
the structure there so you can see what
那里的结构，所以你可以看到
see what the point is this case is kind
看看这种情况有什么意义
of useful if you have two methods that
如果您有两种方法可以
return optional values so the first one
返回可选值，所以第一个
if the optional value is ends up being
如果可选值最终被
empty go to a different method to get
空去另一种方法来获得
another optional value and then of
另一个可选值，然后
course you can carry on chaining this
当然你可以进行链接
and do whatever else you were going to
并做其他你想做的事
do over an optional so it doesn't just
做一个可选的，所以它不只是
terminate with an unwrapped optional so
以解包后的可选内容终止，因此
that's that can be very useful for some
这对于某些人可能非常有用
of the use cases that I've been looking
我一直在寻找的用例
at and one of the other new methods is
在，另一种新方法是
previously well so the the naive way of
以前很好，所以天真的方法
using optional is let's have a look at
使用可选的让我们来看看
this we say if optional is present
我们说这是可选的
optional let's say do something optional
让我们说做一些可选的事情
get let's create that method so this is
让我们创建该方法，这是
kind of the the initial way that you
最初的方式
start using optional if optional is
如果可选是，则开始使用可选
there then do something with the
然后用
optional value IntelliJ tells you well
可选值IntelliJ告诉你很好
that's not a very Java eight way to do
这不是Java的八种方法
stuff and that's what's copy that
东西，那就是复制的东西
IntelliJ tells you that's not very Java
IntelliJ告诉您不是Java
eight ways to do stuff so why don't you
八种做事的方式，为什么不呢
turn that into an if present that's kind
把它变成一个如果存在的那种
of fine that's nice it works reasonably
很好，这很合理
well except for when you wanted to do do
好，除了你想做的时候
something else let's create that method
让我们创建那个方法
then you can no longer use a functional
那么您将无法再使用功能
style expression you have to use the
风格表达，你必须使用
that is present else for now in Java
在Java中目前还存在
nine you can you can use something more
九，你可以使用更多的东西
functional let's turn that back into our
功能让我们把它变成我们的
functional style expression and we use
功能样式表达，我们使用
the new method on Java 9 which is if
Java 9上的新方法是
present or else and you give it your
礼物，否则你给它你的
else condition so if it's present do
其他条件，所以如果存在的话
this if it's not present do that and I
如果不存在，请这样做，而我
think this is really nice because this
认为这真的很好，因为
can really collapse down most
真的可以崩溃
complicated if-else conditions there
那里复杂的if-else条件
I've seen a lot of an existing code that
我看过很多现有的代码
uses null values we were running out of
使用我们用完的空值
time and I just wanted to have a look at
时间，我只想看看
few more features and there's another
几个功能，还有另一个
value which is optional stream this
值，这是可选流
allows you to use optionals more
让您更多地使用可选
effectively in lot surprisingly extreme
有效地出乎意料地极端
operations if I give you if I show you
如果我给你，我就给你
an example that might help so I don't
一个例子可能会有所帮助，所以我不
need you to understand this and we'll
需要您了解这一点，我们会
come back to this code in a second but
稍后再回到此代码，
what I have here is arguments returns me
我在这里的是论点使我返回
as an optional of string array and in
作为字符串数组和in的可选
order to use that effectively inside the
为了在内部有效地使用
stream I ended up calling the the stream
流我最终叫流
method it I'm sure there are more
方法，我确定还有更多
efficient ways of doing this but this
有效的方式做到这一点，但这
was better than the Java 8 wave text so
比Java 8 Wave文本更好，所以
are three methods on stream on
有三种在线播放方法
our optional dough or if present or else
我们的可选面团，如果有的话
an optional ducks dream and they just
可选的鸭子梦，他们只是
mean that it's just going to be a lot
意味着将会很多
easier to work with optionals without
更容易使用可选选项而无需
having to unwrap them and see what the
不得不拆开它们，看看
value is first okay the stack walking
值首先是可以的
API so we just had a really quick hint
API，因此我们有了一个非常快速的提示
of this I know we were looking at
我知道我们在看
monitor and let's have a look
监控，让我们看一下
we know that processing the stack trace
我们知道处理堆栈跟踪
is expensive if you want to look at the
如果你想看看是昂贵的
whole stack trace it has to build the
整个堆栈跟踪它必须建立
whole stack trace and that's expensive
整个堆栈跟踪，这很昂贵
and sometimes what you want to do is you
有时候你想做的就是你
want to look at some part of the stack
想看一下堆栈的某些部分
trace and maybe find the first instance
跟踪并找到第一个实例
of something in the stack or maybe just
堆中的东西，或者可能只是
find who called me so now there's this
找到谁打给我的，所以现在有这个
new thing called a stack walker which
新的东西称为堆栈沃克
lets you lazily look at what's in the
让您懒洋洋地看着里面的东西
stack I highly recommend that you look
堆栈我强烈建议您看
at the the documentation and some blog
在文档和一些博客上
posts around this stuff because again
围绕这个东西发帖，因为再次
this is quite a big a big feature but
这是一个很大的很大的功能，但是
it's worth knowing that now in Java 9
值得一提的是，现在在Java 9中
you can lazily walk the stack so you
你可以懒洋洋地走栈，所以你
don't have to you don't have to incur
不必你也不必招致
the cost of building up the whole stack
建立整个堆栈的成本
trace process API updates we'll go back
跟踪流程API更新，我们将返回
to this code we just saw here and then
我们刚刚在这里看到的这段代码
here there's a whole bunch of new
这里有一堆新的
features around handling processes in in
内处理流程的功能
Java 9 but there's this thing called
Java 9但有一个叫做
process handle which came in to Java 9
Java 9中引入的处理句柄
and this can give this gives us really
这可以使我们真正
useful powerful high-level abstraction
有用的强大高级抽象
over the processes which are running on
对正在运行的进程
our system this is really useful for
我们的系统对于
things like monitoring but I can imagine
诸如监控之类的东西，但我可以想象
a whole bunch of of use cases so here I
一堆用例，所以我在这里
can get all my processes and then I can
可以获得我所有的流程，然后我可以
do stream like operations on it for
为它做流式操作
example let's run this and see what
例子让我们运行它，看看
happens and I get all the processes I
发生了，我得到了所有的过程
want to find all of my processes I want
想找到我想要的所有过程
to find all of my processes which Java
找到我所有的Java进程
processes and I want to find all of my
流程，我想找到我所有的
processes which Java processes which are
哪些Java进程是
my code so if I was running more than
我的代码，所以如果我正在运行超过
one service this would be able to show
一项可以显示的服务
me which services are running the super
我哪些服务正在运行超级
useful in terms of for example micro
在微观方面很有用
services architecture where I might want
我可能想要的服务架构
to see how many of my Microsoft's is
看看我的微软有多少
are running on my on my system so here
在我的系统上运行，所以这里
I'm just running one which is this
我正在运行一个
monitor but and you can also do things
监视，但您也可以执行操作
like you can get the pit for that and
就像你可以为此而坑
then you can process you can process the
然后您可以处理
process you can do things with that
过程中你可以做的事情
process so another really nice feature
过程，所以另一个非常好的功能
here is I get my current process and I
这是我当前的流程，我
can get the process ID of my current
可以获得我当前的进程ID
process which was really difficult in
这个过程真的很难
Java before particularly because you
Java之前特别是因为您
didn't know which operating system
不知道哪个操作系统
you're running on and you didn't know
你在跑，你不知道
how to necessarily manipulate that
如何一定要操纵
operating system so the new process API
操作系统，因此新的流程API
gives you a much higher level way of
给您更高层次的方式
doing sort of operating system stuff
做某种操作系统的东西
which is really useful for things like
这对于诸如
monitoring I knew we would run out of
监视我知道我们会用光
time I'm going to I'm going to expect
我要去的时间
some users are going to want to drop off
一些用户想要下车
because we're running out of time but
因为我们没时间了，但是
I'm going to try and finish this and of
我将尝试完成
course it will be recorded so if you
当然会被记录下来，所以如果你
have to drop off you can come back in
必须下车你可以回来
later and and see the recording I'm just
稍后再看录音，我只是
trying to see how many more things just
试图看看还有多少东西
a few more things and then we get to the
还有一些事情，然后我们去
summary Matsu released jar files um let
摘要Matsu发布了jar文件um let
me open up an application which
我打开一个应用程序
demonstrates this so Martin released jar
演示了这一点，所以马丁释放了罐子
files is a as a new feature in Java 9
文件是Java 9中的一项新功能
which i think is really cool and I wish
我认为这真的很酷，我希望
we'd had it much earlier this is the
我们早就拥有了
ability for a library to release a
库发布内容的能力
single jar file which contains different
包含不同内容的单个jar文件
implementations with different versions
不同版本的实现
of the JVM so for example people who are
的JVM，例如
using Java not Java 9 basically Java 8
使用Java而不是Java 9基本上是Java 8
and below they will run the jar file and
在下面，他们将运行jar文件，
they will get the Java 8 or pre Java 9
他们将获得Java 8或Java 9之前的版本
functionality and if you are running
功能以及您是否正在运行
Java 9 then when you run that same jar
Java 9然后当您运行相同的jar时
file you'll get the Java 9 functionality
文件，您将获得Java 9功能
now theoretically this is only supposed
现在从理论上讲这只是假设
to work for the internals for the way
为内部人员工作
that the implementation works you
该实施对您有效
shouldn't get a different API if you're
如果您正在使用，则不应获取其他API
running on Java 8 or Java 9 I believe
我相信可以在Java 8或Java 9上运行
that might be down to standards rather
可能不符合标准
than an actual implementation
比实际的实现
restriction so I'd be really interested
限制，所以我会很感兴趣
to see how these things are implemented
看看这些东西是如何实现的
by library developments but I'll just
根据图书馆的发展，但我只是
really quickly
真的很快
show you the mechanics of it because
向您展示其原理，因为
it's it's fairly fairly simple so I have
这是相当简单的，所以我有
a project I'm going to write a blog post
一个我要写博客文章的项目
about this about how to do this in
关于如何做到这一点
IntelliJ because it's quite interesting
IntelliJ，因为它很有趣
so I have a project this is my code it
所以我有一个项目，这是我的代码
happens to be compiled and run in Java I
碰巧是在Java中编译并运行的
have a main class I have I have an
有一个主班我有一个
interface stack info and then my stack
接口堆栈信息，然后是我的堆栈
parser for anything which is running on
解析器，用于运行任何内容
Java 8 users get current thread to get
Java 8用户获取当前线程以获取
the stack trace that's the
堆栈跟踪是
implementation that I've chosen there
我在那里选择的实现
and what I've got here is I have an
我在这里有一个
implementation and stack parser for Java
Java的实现和堆栈解析器
9 which is the stack Walker that I just
9这就是我刚刚所走的堆栈Walker
showed you
给你看
so obviously the stack Walker will be
所以很明显堆栈Walker将
more efficient so if you're running Java
效率更高，因此如果您正在运行Java
9 I want you to be able to run this
9我希望您能够运行此程序
using the Java 9 implementation and the
使用Java 9实现和
way that's done is my classes for the
完成的方式是我的课程
normal code goes in the normal sort of
普通代码以普通形式出现
routes the normal structure of your
路由您的正常结构
classes my job and I on specific code I
根据特定的代码对我的工作进行分类
don't have to compile the whole project
不必编译整个项目
app down to Java 9 just my java 9
应用程序降到Java 9只是我的Java 9
specific stuff and it goes into
具体的东西，它进入
meta-chem version 9 and potentially you
元化学版本9，可能还有您
could have like 10 11 12 in there if you
如果你有10 11 12
want to what you can't have is you can't
想拥有你所不能拥有的
have 8 7 and 6 because this only applies
有8 7和6，因为这仅适用
from 9 onwards which is very sad and but
从9开始，这是非常可悲的，但是
you can see so here my step father is
你可以看到所以我继父是
compiled with Java 8 it's my Java 8
用Java 8编译的是我的Java 8
class and this stack parser is my job a
类，这个堆栈解析器是我的工作
9 class and then in my manifest I say
9课，然后在我的清单中我说
this is a multi release jar file and
这是一个多版本的jar文件，
then I build my jar file and when I run
然后我建立我的jar文件，当我运行
it if I run this in Java 8
如果我在Java 8中运行它
I get the Java 8 implementation which is
我得到了Java 8实现
you'd which uses Java dot land of thread
您使用的是Java点线程
and if I run it in Java 9
如果我在Java 9中运行它
I get the job and I on implementation so
我得到了这份工作，我正在实施
and that's just using the same jar file
那只是使用相同的jar文件
so I think this is a really interesting
所以我觉得这真的很有趣
feature of Java 9 and I'd be really
9的功能，我真的会
interested to see if that will help
有兴趣看看是否有帮助
library is migrated to use Java 9
库已迁移为使用Java 9
features and more quickly than they
功能比它们更快
would previously have been able to do
本来可以做到的
updated deprecation this is this will
更新弃用，这将是
help us as developers trying to trying
帮助我们作为开发人员尝试
to figure out which features we should
找出我们应该使用的功能
and shouldn't be using so let's have a
并且不应该使用，所以让我们
look at current threads dot
看当前线程点
stop let's say and then you can see
停止说，然后您可以看到
maybe you can see our own color right
也许你可以看到我们自己的颜色
this is actually crossed out in red as
这实际上是用红色划掉的
opposed to in black and it says it's
反对用黑色，它说这是
deprecated and marks for removal if we
如果我们不赞成使用，则将其标记为删除
look at this the deprecated annotation
看看这个不推荐使用的注解
that has two new properties the person
有两个新属性的人
who deprecated the person who deprecated
不赞成的人不赞成的人
it could optionally say which version it
它可以选择说出它的版本
was deprecated in and is this code going
已不赞成使用，此代码是否正在运行
away theoretically you can deprecated
从理论上讲，您可以弃用
something in a kind of well don't really
某种东西不是真的
use this but I'm not going to get rid of
用这个，但我不会摆脱
it whereas now you can flag it for this
它，而现在您可以为此标记它
method is going away so if you're using
方法正在消失，所以如果您使用
it you really do need to stop using it
您确实需要停止使用它
right now and this is going to be really
现在，这将是真正的
useful for helping us to move away from
有助于我们摆脱困境
using old code and figure out how
使用旧代码并弄清楚如何
important it is that we that we do that
重要的是我们做到这一点
for example if we use the other version
例如，如果我们使用其他版本
of this
这个的
and we look in it says is deprecated but
我们看它说已弃用，但
it's not going away
它不会消失
it's a small fix but it makes life a bit
这是一个小小的解决办法，但它会使生活变得有点
easier html5 Javadoc dragging Javadoc
更轻松的html5 Javadoc拖动Javadoc
kicking and screaming into the 21st
踢到21世纪
century and this allows us to generate
世纪，这使我们能够产生
our Javadoc in html5 so you end up with
html5中的Javadoc，因此您最终获得了
something which looks more like this
看起来更像这样的东西
that's kind of nice and you know it's
很好，你知道
cool but what's most interesting about
很酷，但是最有趣的是
it is this feature Java Docs search and
正是此功能Java Docs搜索和
I can do camelcase search like I'm used
我可以像过去一样进行驼峰式搜索
to have from having IntelliJ IDEA and I
拥有IntelliJ IDEA和我
can search for the classes I'm actually
可以搜索我实际所在的课程
interested in inside Java doc this is so
对Java doc感兴趣的是
much better than having to open it up
比必须打开它要好得多
into the frames and then do a find in
进入框架，然后在
page just to find something that I know
页面只是为了找到我知道的东西
is probably there and I just really want
可能在那里，我真的很想要
to be able to get to it so this is a
能够做到这一点，所以这是一个
really really nice feature again one of
真的真的很不错的功能之一
those small things we just come into
我们刚遇到的那些小事
Java now it's just going to make life a
Java现在将使生活变得更加美好
lot easier for us and yes so that's that
对我们来说要容易得多，是的，那就是
JTL we are way over time so I don't have
JTL我们随着时间流逝，所以我没有
time to demonstrate Jojo which is really
是时候演示Jojo了
sad because I never have time to
悲伤，因为我没有时间去
demonstrate Jason J shell and but this
演示Jason J shell，但这
is the repple and you'll be able to see
是乳头，您将能够看到
these links when we when we put the
这些链接，当我们把
slides out later and Jay Chou allows you
稍后滑出，周杰伦允许您
to run from the command line so I can
从命令行运行，所以我可以
run J tail from the command line which
从命令行运行J tail
is it's something that comes as part of
这是它的一部分吗
Java 9 obviously so I'm going to run it
Java 9很明显，所以我要运行它
from here and I could say I can say
从这里，我可以说我可以说
system.out.print learn whoops I'd get
system.out.print学习我会听到的声音
tab completion which is kind of nice
制表符补全，很好
because I'm lazy and I could say hello
因为我很懒，我可以打个招呼
and I don't need a semicolon which is
而且我不需要分号
amazing but there's loads of other stuff
很棒，但是还有很多其他的东西
enjoy so what I think is really
享受，所以我认为真的
interesting from an intelligent of view
从聪明的角度来看很有趣
is we do have a tool which uses this so
是我们有使用该工具的工具吗
we have J shell console which allows us
我们有J Shell控制台，它允许我们
to do something similar so we get system
做类似的事情，所以我们得到系统
dot out dot println hello and we can do
点出点println你好，我们可以做
the same thing so this allows us to play
同样的事情，所以这允许我们玩
around with functionality well before we
在我们使用功能之前
actually have to put it into our
实际上必须将其放入我们的
production code so we can run snippets
生产代码，以便我们可以运行摘要
and we can we can potentially create
我们可以潜在地创造
scripts and so forth it's a really
脚本等等，这真的是
interesting feature that we haven't had
我们没有的有趣功能
in Java before and from our point of
在我们之前和之后的Java中
view
视图
it'd be really useful if you use this
如果你用这个的话真的很有用
really useful for you to feedback to us
对您反馈给我们非常有用
to tell us well obviously if there are
告诉我们很明显是否
any bugs but what's more interesting is
任何错误，但更有趣的是
what sort of features do you want to see
您想看到什么样的功能
what kind of things and how do you use
什么样的东西以及如何使用
it how can we make your workflow easier
它如何使您的工作流程更轻松
okay well over time
好的，随着时间的流逝
let's now summarize Java 9 people are
现在让我们总结一下Java 9人
afraid of Java 9 because they've been
害怕Java 9，因为他们一直
meaning for years that code is going to
意味着多年的代码将
break so that's what people are afraid
休息，所以人们害怕
of that your code is going to break
您的代码将被破坏
because of the encapsulation of internal
因为内部封装
api is because of a number of different
api是因为许多不同
things now of course the the key thing
现在的事情当然是关键
to do is try it out and find out whether
要做的就是尝试一下，找出是否
your code is going to break and don't
您的代码将被破坏，不要
just wait and see because no one's going
只是拭目以待，因为没有人去
to be able to tell you that your code is
能够告诉您您的代码是
broken and in which way it is broken and
坏了，用什么方式坏了，
it is well worth trying it out now
现在值得尝试
especially now that Java 9 is out
特别是在Java 9发布之后
officially and it's not an early access
正式的，这不是早期的尝试
release which is going to change there
发行将在那里改变
are a number of things which could
有很多事情可以
contribute to your code breaking there's
有助于破坏您的代码
a lot of things which are going away so
很多东西要消失了，所以
removal of deprecated GC combinations
删除过时的GC组合
for example removing various tools
例如删除各种工具
removing various launch time flags
删除各种启动时间标志
deprecating the applet api these are
弃用applet API，这些是
things they're going away so and they
他们要离开的事情，所以他们
encapsulate most internal api is is the
封装的大多数内部api是
thing which basically makes some things
基本上可以制造某些东西的东西
that you were using potentially look
你正在使用的潜在外观
like they've gone away what's more
就像他们已经消失了一样
interesting that might cause unexpected
可能会导致意外的有趣
breakages is some of these features
破损是其中的一些特征
which which might change the behavior of
这可能会改变行为
your application without you realizing
您的应用程序没有意识到
it so they did a lot of work on the JVM
所以他们在JVM上做了很多工作
logging so if you've got anything like
记录，所以如果你有类似的东西
reports running correcting for various
报告运行纠正各种
log statements or anything like that
日志语句或类似的内容
those might not be there anymore in Java
那些在Java中可能不再存在
9 and things like g1 is the default
9和默认值g1之类的东西
garbage collector I don't think that's
垃圾收集器，我不认为那是
really going to impact a lot of people
真的会影响很多人
because if you don't care very much
因为如果你不在乎
about your garbage collector so you're
关于你的垃圾收集器，所以你
using the default
使用默认
I don't think changing the default will
我认为更改默认设置不会
make a big difference and if you do care
有很大的不同，如果你在乎
about your garbage collector you've
关于你的垃圾收集器
probably tuned it within an inch of its
可能在不到一英寸的范围内对其进行了调整
life so you don't really care what the
生活，所以你真的不在乎什么
default is because you're not using it
默认是因为您不使用它
and but it is worth being aware of to me
但是值得我注意
one of the gotchas that certainly got a
肯定有一个陷阱
lot of tools and frameworks and
很多工具和框架，以及
libraries is the new version string
库是新版本的字符串
scheme so Java 9 is not Java 1.9 Java 9
方案，因此Java 9不是Java 1.9 Java 9
is Java 9 so if you're doing any parsing
是Java 9，所以如果您要进行任何解析
of the version string and taking the 1
版本字符串并取1
point off the beginning and to find out
指出起点并找出答案
what version it is
它是什么版本
that's not going to work with Java 9 you
那将无法在Java 9中使用
are going to get like an index out of
像索引一样
bounds exception or something it's you
界限异常或某事是你
can't take the 1.9 off the beginning
一开始就无法摆脱1.9
because it doesn't exist and of course
因为它不存在，当然
this is going to be even more
这将更加
interesting when Java 10 comes out since
有趣的是，Java 10发布以来
they're talking about calling it Java
他们正在谈论称其为Java
18.3 the tools the libraries the
18.3工具库
frameworks continues delivery things the
框架继续交付东西
stuff that we rely on are still evolving
我们所依赖的东西还在不断发展
for Java 9 there's been a lot of churn
对于Java 9来说，流失很多
in Java 9 in the last year alone
仅在去年的Java 9中
it hasn't been super stable the China's
它不是中国的超级稳定
been good because it's made Java 9
很好，因为它是Java 9
better and stronger for what it is but
更好，更强大，但是
some of the tools and frameworks were
一些工具和框架是
waiting for it to settle down before
等待它安定下来之前
becoming Java 9 compliant so do try it
兼容Java 9，请尝试一下
particularly in your continuous
特别是在你连续不断
integration environment make sure that
集成环境确保
CI still works make sure that the
CI仍然有效，请确保
libraries are working the way you expect
库以您期望的方式工作
them to so and then you probably need to
他们如此，然后您可能需要
upgrade to the latest version of some of
升级到一些最新版本
the things that you're using
您正在使用的东西
you don't need to modularize your code
您不需要模块化代码
in order to use Java 9 this is a common
为了使用Java 9，这很常见
misconception you don't need to put
误解，你不需要放
module - info Java into your code in
模块-信息Java到您的代码中
order to use the collections factory
为了使用收藏工厂
methods for example you don't need to
例如，您不需要的方法
use any of the motorisation stuff if you
使用任何机动化的东西，如果你
want to just use the features in Java 9
只想使用Java 9中的功能
like new methods on optional new methods
像新方法上的可选新方法
on string so if motorisation isn't going
串起来，所以如果不动力化
to give you any benefits using the new
给您带来新的好处
module system isn't going to give you
模块系统不会给你
any benefits don't use it because it is
任何好处都不要使用它，因为它是
quite a lot of work and one of the
大量的工作，其中之一
reasons why Java 9 well why the module
为什么Java 9很好为什么模块
system was pushed out to Java 9 from
系统从推出到Java 9
Java 7 is it took them a long time to
Java 7是他们花了很长时间
modularize the jdk itself so it is a lot
模块化jdk本身，所以很多
of work but you don't need to so don't
工作，但您不必如此
do it if you don't have to the game you
如果您不需要玩游戏，那就去做吧
do get good design using Java now it
现在可以使用Java获得良好的设计
does encourage encapsulation separation
确实鼓励封装分离
of concerns good object-oriented design
关注良好的面向对象设计
you get some you get a cleaner design
你得到一些，你得到一个更清洁的设计
from using it you also get better
通过使用它，你也会变得更好
security from that as well so this is
安全性也是如此
definitely a good thing it encourages
绝对是一件好事，它鼓励
new ways of working using the repple
使用乳头的新工作方式
using the right two streams API and
使用正确的两个流API和
things like that
像这样的东西
but I think for me Java 9 is just a bit
但我认为Java 9只是一点点
nicer to write code it's not the sexiest
更好地编写代码不是最性感的
strapline for a version of Java but
Java版本的带状线，但是
that's what it is these things like the
就是这些东西
the new methods an optional and stream
新方法（可选）和流
the collections factory methods the
收藏工厂的方法
reduction of various bits of boilerplate
减少样板的各个位
being able to use effectively final
能够有效地使用final
variables in try with resources the
尝试使用资源变量
ability to use the diamond operator with
可以将Diamond运算符与
anonymous inner classes these are all
匿名内部类都是这些
tiny things but they just start to sweep
小事，但它们才开始席卷
away some of the boilerplate and some of
删除一些样板和一些
the noise from working with Java so this
使用Java产生的噪音
is kind of the main benefit of moving to
是转移到
Java 9 from my point of view and of
从我的角度来看Java 9
course it's a good idea to move to Java
当然，迁移到Java是一个好主意
9 because Java 10 is allegedly going to
9，因为据称Java 10将
come out in March
三月出来
this March coming so we're going to need
今年三月到来，所以我们需要
to have adopted Java 9 and got ourselves
已经采用Java 9并获得了成功
all look at all our libraries upgraded
都看我们所有升级的图书馆
so everything works with Java 9 so that
所以一切都可以在Java 9中使用
we can use all the cool features which
我们可以使用所有很酷的功能
are coming in Java 10 like local type
Java 10即将推出，就像本地类型一样
inference and some of the other cool
推论和其他一些很酷的
stuff which is going to be in Java 10
Java 10中的东西
okay so as usual I am extremely way over
好吧，所以像往常一样，我走的太远了
time this link points to it will point
该链接指向的时间将指向
to this video in this video is online
这个视频在这个视频中在线
this link points to a bunch of stuff
该链接指向一堆东西
like documentation for Jade EPS jailing
像Jade EPS监狱的文档
all of these tools that I've mentioned
我提到的所有这些工具
and the links which were mentioned
和提到的链接
earlier on in terms of tutorials for J
关于J的教程
shell and even other videos of this talk
外壳以及本次演讲的其他视频
where I've been able to go into more
我能够深入了解的地方
depth on reactive programming more depth
反应式编程深度更深
on J shell perhaps so do follow that
在J shell上，也许也可以这样做
link and find more resources there I
链接并在那里找到更多资源
will take questions but I fully expect
会提出问题，但我完全期望
that people have already disappeared
人们已经消失了
because I'm enormously over time
因为我随着时间的流逝
andraia any questions
安德拉亚任何问题
yeah I wish we had more time for
是的，我希望我们有更多时间
questions with what we can do is to try
我们能做的就是尝试
to address most interesting question in
解决最有趣的问题
the blog post which will publish along
该博客文章将随
with the video and yeah and everyone who
视频，是的，还有每个人
registered will get that email and yeah
注册将收到该电子邮件，是的
that's that's it and no doubt it's it's
就是这样，毫无疑问是
quite challenging task to to explain on
要解释的非常具有挑战性的任务
all the features of Java now and in just
现在和仅使用Java的所有功能
one hour
一小时
so you thinks we show you you just yeah
所以你以为我们告诉你你是的
made a great job thank you it's quite
做得很好，谢谢
difficult when jigsaw really should take
当拼图真的应该采取的时候很难
about three hours in its own right yeah
大概三个小时
so thank you really appreciate your time
非常感谢您的宝贵时间
and thanks everyone for joining us
并感谢大家加入我们
thanks a lot all right okay take care
非常感谢，好吧，保重
have a good day
祝你有美好的一天
you
您